<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Baird</title>
    <link>https://mbaird.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Michael Baird</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 13:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mbaird.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 8</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 13:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-8/</guid>
      <description>The pain in my wrists is frustratingly persistent. I need to constantly remind myself not to &amp;lsquo;over exercise&amp;rsquo; as I usually do when it flares up, causing more problems. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken some time off work and tried to minimize time using keyboards, mice and controllers (which means no Apex Legends), but now I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do with myself.
  Walking around the streets in 17-degree sunshine this week provided a little taste of spring, reminding me just how enjoyable London can be when it&amp;rsquo;s not dark, cold and raining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 7</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 12:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-7/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been battling persistent nerve pain in my right wrist this last week, so this will be brief.
  Watching NASA&amp;rsquo;s Perseverance rover landing on Mars provided a rare mid-week treat on Thursday evening. The interactive website simulation showing the rover&amp;rsquo;s &amp;quot;seven minutes of terror&amp;quot; landing at the end of it&amp;rsquo;s 292 million mile trip felt very familiar, having studied the similarly described descent landing for Curiosity rover at university in 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 6</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-6/</guid>
      <description>So I tried out AllPlants on a friends&#39; recommendation this week, and a few days ago was the lucky recipient of six frozen vegan ready meals. As I negotiated them into the freezer like some lockdown themed version of the knapsack problem, I slid back the sleeve on each one to inspect the contents. If the cardboard packaging didn&amp;rsquo;t tell me what was in each one, I&amp;rsquo;d have had no chance of sorting my &amp;lsquo;Spiced Aubergine Tagine&amp;rsquo; from my &amp;lsquo;Thai Green Curry&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 5</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-5/</guid>
      <description>Dan Nguyen&amp;rsquo;s The Bastards Book of Photography has got me itching to head out with my camera again if only it&amp;rsquo;d stop raining. His advice feels honest and considered, recommending you start with whatever you have and start taking photos.
 &amp;ldquo;So shoot whatever you have in front of you. No matter how mundane it is. Practice it from the same angle over and over if you have to but it&amp;rsquo;s better to just try different times of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 4</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 16:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-4/</guid>
      <description>Opting for a slightly different take on the traditional burns night supper, we picked up an assemble-at-home kit of haggis tacos from Mac &amp;amp; Wild. Recollections of Buckfast-fuelled teenage house parties made me apprehensive about &amp;lsquo;Buckfast sriracha hot sauce&amp;rsquo;. Still, it turned out to be fantastic and not at all reminiscent of the strong-smelling, tar-like substance prevalent in my youth.
The kit included a QR code for an accompanying Spotify playlist, mostly featuring the Peatbog Faeries and the Red Hot Chilli Pipers which a friend was quick to brand as &amp;lsquo;tourist pish&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 3</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 14:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-3/</guid>
      <description>The lack of genuine next-gen titles for the Series X has kept me playing Apex Legends (albeit now at an impressive 4K 60fps), bringing my total time spent playing over the last two years to just over 500 hours. I put that down to the terrific job Respawn do of making the game feel fresh and new with regular season updates without ruining the core of the game. Thankfully 10,000 hours is a myth, so I might be well on my way to mastery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 2</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 16:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-2/</guid>
      <description>I have joined Signal, as have a healthy majority of frequent contacts.
  This week I endured my first engagement with Apple&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Feedback Assistant&amp;rsquo;, the bug reporting tool shipped with macOS. Coincidentally, just this week I&amp;rsquo;d listened to ATP #411: Are My Instructions Not Clear?, where the hosts debate the numerous fundamental issues with the process at length. It did not fill me with hope.
The bug in question causes my system to intermittently hang for 1 - 2 seconds when typing into the Safari address bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes 1</title>
      <link>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 19:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mbaird.github.io/posts/weeknotes-1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been keen to try writing weeknotes for a couple of reasons: mostly as a way to improve my written communication, but I also think I&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy a regular nudge to reflect on each week as they happen.
  Slack weren&amp;rsquo;t the only ones with website problems this week after a late-evening SMS told me our website at work was completely down. Initial inspection showed that our tiny Heroku set up of just 2 small dynos had been overwhelmed by traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
